<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

<channel>
  <atom:link href="http://www.principledsocietiesproject.org/Data/psp_rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <title>Principled Societies Project</title>
  <link>http://www.PrincipledSocietiesProject.org/blog</link>
  <description>Empowering Individuals, Organizations, and Communities Solve Problems That Matter</description>
  <copyright>Creative Commons Attribution-NoDerivatives 4.0 International License</copyright>


  <item>
    <title>Is Solving Problems the Ideal of Democracy and Capitalism?</title>
    <link>http://www.PrincipledSocietiesProject.org/ideals_democracy_capitalism</link>
    <guid>http://www.PrincipledSocietiesProject.org/ideals_democracy_capitalism</guid>
    <description>Societies can solve important problems. Doing so is the essence of sustainability. But systems innovation is necessary.
    </description>
  </item>

  <item>
    <title>Solving Problems That Matter Could Be the Next Big Thing</title>
    <link>http://www.PrincipledSocietiesProject.org/socio_prospectus</link>
    <guid>http://www.PrincipledSocietiesProject.org/socio_prospectus</guid>
    <description>By viewing a society as a problem-solving superorganism, the natural sciences and technology sector can go wild with possibilities. Designs of economic, governance, and legal systems fall into their domain. 
    </description>
  </item>


  <item>
    <title>An Economy of Meaning, or Bust</title>
    <link>http://www.PrincipledSocietiesProject.org/economy_of_meaning</link>
    <guid>http://www.PrincipledSocietiesProject.org/economy_of_meaning</guid>
    <description>Current economic systems are dismal because they waste our precious time. We can pause to reevaluate, and redesign.
    </description>
  </item>

  <item>
    <title>Wellbeing Centrality: Toward an Economics and Politics of Meaning</title>
    <link>http://www.PrincipledSocietiesProject.org/wellbeing_centrality_summary</link>
    <guid>http://www.PrincipledSocietiesProject.org/wellbeing_centrality_summary</guid>
    <description>The designs of current economic and governance systems may be inadequate to solve our many pressing problems. Ideas from complex systems science and other fields can help us re-conceptualize systems, leading to better designs.
    </description>
  </item>

  <item>
    <title>Why Stop at Basic Income and a Living Wage?</title>
    <link>http://www.PrincipledSocietiesProject.org/why_stop_at_basic_income</link>
    <guid>http://www.PrincipledSocietiesProject.org/why_stop_at_basic_income</guid>
    <description> We can ask the big question: Out of all conceivable economic system designs, which ones might be best at helping us to focus on and solve problems that matter?
    </description>
  </item>    
  
</channel>

</rss> 
